{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "I", "answer": "am" },
    { "prompt": "you", "answer": "are" },
    { "prompt": "he", "answer": "is" },
    { "prompt": "she", "answer": "is" },
    { "prompt": "it", "answer": "is" },
    { "prompt": "am", "answer": "I" },
    { "prompt": "are", "answer": "you" },
    { "prompt": "is", "answer": "he/she/it" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "I", "answer": "have" },
    { "prompt": "you", "answer": "have" },
    { "prompt": "he", "answer": "has" },
    { "prompt": "she", "answer": "has" },
    { "prompt": "it", "answer": "has" },
    { "prompt": "have", "answer": "I/you" },
    { "prompt": "has", "answer": "he/she/it" }
  ],
  "9": [
    { "prompt": "I", "answer": "go" },
    { "prompt": "you", "answer": "go" },
    { "prompt": "he", "answer": "goes" },
    { "prompt": "she", "answer": "goes" },
    { "prompt": "it", "answer": "goes" },
    { "prompt": "go", "answer": "I/you" },
    { "prompt": "goes", "answer": "he/she/it" }
  ]
}